Goal of the United Nations aims to
ensure global sustainable access to
modern, reliable, affordable and
clean energy. The lack of sustainable,
reliable and secure energy services is
a serious challenge globally.
Achieving this goal requires
providing renewable energy,
improving energy efficiency and
promoting clean energy technology.
China is the largest wind power market
in the world, with a wind power installed capacity
of 210 GW in 2019,
accounting for 35% of global capacity.
The Chinese government has vigorously promoted
renewable energy and has become the world's
largest producer of solar and wind energy.
The government has taken a series of measures,
such as implementing clean energy policies and
providing tax breaks,
to encourage the development of renewable energy.
However, the development of clean energy also
faces some challenges. The instability of
renewable energy and how to solve energy storage
and distribution problems
are still difficult problems.
Traditional energy is cheap and
has a high usage rate, and many people
still use non-clean energy.
To overcome these challenges,
the Chinese government has taken measures
such as increasing investment and
research and development
in energy storage technology to solve
the instability of renewable energy.
The government is also strengthening
the promotion and education of
clean energy to improve public awareness
and acceptance.
China has already achieved some
successful cases in clean energy.
For example, in 2019, renewable energy
accounted for 28.2% of total
electricity consumption,
far exceeding the UN's target.
In addition, China has established
the world's largest wind and
solar power station, contributing to
the development of global clean energy.
Achieving the 7th Sustainable Development Goal of
the United Nations requires global cooperation
and coordination, as well as the support and
efforts of governments and the public in
various countries.
By strengthening policy and technical support
and improving public awareness and
acceptance of clean energy,
we can jointly achieve the goal of
global sustainable energy.